1. Dear Father, who hast made us all,
To Thee Thy children humbly pray:
Look on this babe who at Thy call
Now enters on life's narrow way.

2. Dear Savior, for Thy love un - told,
We bring this little child to Thee.
Receive it, Shepherd, to Thy fold
And keep it Thine eternally.

3. Dear Spirit, rest upon this child,
As Thou didst brood upon the Sea,
And make it pure and undefiled,
A holy temple unto Thee.

4. O Triune God, we humbly pray,
That all Thy blessings be conferred,
Upon this child here cleansed to - day,
By means of water and the Word