1. He leadeth me! Oh, blessed thought!
Oh, words with heavenly comfort fraught!
What - e'er I do, where'er I be,
Still ‘tis God's hand that leadeth me.

Ch: He leadeth me! He leadeth me!
By His own hand He leadeth me;
His faithful follower I would be,
For by His hand He leadeth me.

2. Some - times ‘mid scenes of deepest gloom,
Some - times where Eden's bowers bloom,
By waters calm, o'er troubled sea
Still ‘tis God's hand that leadeth me.

3. Lord, I would clasp Thy hand in mine,
Nor ever murmur, nor repine;
Content, what - ever lot I see,
Since ‘tis my God that leadeth me.

4. And when my task on earth is done,
When, by Thy grace, the victory's won,
E'en death's cold wave I will not flee,
Since Thou thro' Jordan leadest me.