1. Lord Jesus Christ, be present now,
Our hearts in true devotion bow,
Thy Spirit send with grace divine,
And let Thy truth within us shine.

2. Unseal our lips to sing Thy praise,
Our souls to Thee in worship raise,
Make strong our faith, increase our light,
That we may know Thy name aright.

3. Until we join the hosts that cry,
“Holy art Thou, O Lord, most high!”
And in the light of that blest place
Fore'er behold Thee face to face.

4. Glory to God the Father, Son,
And Holy Spirit, Three in One!.
To Thee, 0 blessed Trinity,
Be praise throughout eternity!